Guide to Records Concerning Real Property and Legal Transactions near Cripple Creek, Colorado
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Records of Unidentified Abstract Companies, 1861-1940; Series II; 32.9; (107 boxes)
  - Abstract Records of Teller County, 1891-1937
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date, 1899-1933
      - Second Set, 1899-1933
        - Volume 26, Pages 1-250, Entries 48874-50408, 1904 February 23-June 28 (Box 139, Folder 390)
        - Volume 26, Pages 251-500, Entries 50409-51913, 1904 June 28- November 29 (Box 139, Folder 391)
        - Volume 26, Pages 501-750, Entries 51915-53894, 1904 November 29-1905 April 22 (Box 139, Folder 392)
        - Volume 26, Pages 751-1000, Entries 53895-56323, 1905 April 22-November 14 (Box 139, Folder 393)
        - Volume 27, Pages 1-250, Entries 56324-58610, 1905 November 4-1906 May 18 (Box 139, Folder 394)
          Laid-in items include notes about the foreclosure sale of Colorado Electric Power Co. to W. S. Mitchell on July 5, 1904, and typescript of a decree regarding Larry Maroney v. The Gold Mining Stock Exchange on April 25, 1906.
        - Volume 27, Pages 251-500, Entries 58611-60430, 1906 May 18-December 8 (Box 139, Folder 395)
        - Volume 27, Pages 501-750, Entries 60431-61927, 1906 December 8-1907 May 13 (Box 140, Folder 396)
        - Volume 27, Pages 751-1000, Entries 61928-63392, 1907 May 14-December 10 (Box 140, Folder 397)
        - Volume 28, Pages 1-250, Entries 63393-65210, 1907 December 10-1908 June 26 (Box 140, Folder 398)
        - Volume 28, Pages 251-500, Entries 65211-67322, 1908 June 27-1909 February 1 (Box 140, Folder 399)
        - Volume 28, Pages 501-750, Entries 67324-69694, 1909 February 2-October 4 (Box 140, Folder 400)
        - Volume 28, Page 751-1000, Entries 69687-71891, 1909 October 5-1910 May 19 (Box 140, Folder 401)
        - Volume 29, Pages 1-246, Entries 71892-73885, 1910 May 20-1911 January 11 (Box 141, Folder 402)
        - Volume 29, Pages 247-500, Entries 73886-75907, 1910 January 12-1911 August 30 (Box 141, Folder 403)
        - Volume 29, Pages 501-750, Entries 75908-78198, 1911 August 31-1912 April 29 (Box 141, Folder 404)
        - Volume 29, Pages 751-100, Entries 78200-80611, 1912 April 30-1913 January 28 (Box 141, Folder 405)
        - Volume 30, Pages 1-500, Entries 80612-85937, 1913 January 28-1914 August 13 (Box 141, Folder 406)
        - Volume 30, Pages 501-689, Entries 85948-87986, 1914 August 14-1915 March 24 (Box 141, Folder 407)
        - Volume 30, Pages 690-1000, Entries 87987-91209, 1915 March 25-1916 February 9 (Box 142, Folder 408)
        - Volume 31, Pages 1-343, Entries 91210-95000, 1916 February 10-1917 January 26 (Box 142, Folder 409)
        - Volume 32, Pages 1-250, Entries 95001-96896, 1917 January 27-July 18 (Box 142, Folder 410)
        - Volume 32, Pages 251-371, Entries 96897-97962, 1917 July 19-November 30 (Box 142, Folder 411)
        - Volume 32, Pages 372-507, Entries 97965-99752, 1917 December 3-1918 June 29 (Box 142, Folder 412)
        - Volume 32, Pages 508-619, Entries 99753-100868, 1918 July 1-December 31 (Box 143, Folder 413)
        - Volume 32, Pages 620-740, Entries 100869-101746, 1919 January 3-June 28 (Box 143, Folder 414)
        - Volume 10, Pages 741-862, Entries 101749-102521, 1919 July 1-October 31 (Box 143, Folder 415)
        - Volume 11, Pages 863-1009, Entries 102522-103452, 1919 November 1-1920 April 30 (Box 143, Folder 416)
        - Volume 12, Pages 1010-unnumbered, Entries 103453-104593, 1920 May 3-December 31 (Box 143, Folder 417)
        - Volume 13, Entries 104594-105422, 1921 January 3-June 30 (Box 143, Folder 418)
        - Volume 14, Entries 105423-106142, 1921 July 1-December 31 (Box 144, Folder 419)
        - Volume 15, Entries 106143-107451, 1922 January 3-November 25 (Box 144, Folder 420)
        - Volume 16, Entries 107452-109026, 1922 November 25-1924 January 3 (Box 144, Folder 421)
          Laid-in a special master's deed from Igor O. Wingren and George M. Taylor to W. D. Corley, recorded November 27, 1922, and a quit claim deed from Thomas Kavanaugh to The Ironclad Hill Mining and Development Company, recorded November 27, 1922.
        - Volume 17, Entries 109027-113004, 1924 January 5-1926 January 6 (Box 144, Folder 422)
          - Laid-In Material from Volume 17, 1924-1926 (Box 145, Folder 423-450)
            Consists of legal instruments reflected in the volume.
        - Volume 18, Entries 113005-115132, 1926 January 7-December 13 (Box 145, Folder 451)
        - Volume 19, Entries 115133- 118615, 1926 December 13-1928 August 10 (Box 145, Folder 452)
        - Volume 20, Entries 118616-121846, 1928 August 10-1930 September 5 (Box 145, Folder 453)
        - Volume 21, Entries 121847-123470, 1930 September 5-1931 November 13 (Box 146, Folder 454)
        - Volume 22, Entries 123471-124400, 1931 November 13-1932 August 15 (Box 146, Folder 455)
        - Volume 23, Entries 124401-125771, 1932 August 15-1933 September 22 (Box 146, Folder 456)
    - Delinquent Tax Lists, 1903-1922
      Arranged chronologically
      Within each volume lists are arranged alphabetically by subject or location.
      Clippings of delinquent tax lists from the Cripple Creek Times, Victor Daily Record, and the The Times-Record newspapers. The lists often include listings for delinquent taxes for previous years.
      Some volumes contain multiple years. Some years appear across different volumes.
      - Volume 1902-1906, 1903 October 13-1907 October 24 (Box 147, Folder 457)
      - Volume 1905, 1906 October 31 (Box 147, Folder 458)
      - Volume 1907, 1907 October 19 (Box 148, Folder 459)
      - Volume 1908, 1909 October 15 (Box 148, Folder 460)
      - Volume 1909, 1910 October (Box 149, Folder 461)
      - Volume 1910, 1911 October 18 (Box 149, Folder 462)
      - Volume 1911-1913, 1912 October-1914 October (Box 149, Folder 463)
      - Volume 1918-1919, 1918 October 23-1920 October 23 (Box 150, Folder 464)
      - Volume 1921, 1922 November 23 (Box 150, Folder 465)
    - Sale Records for Delinquent Tax, 1902-1908
      Material under this heading is arranged into three sets: First Set, 1890-1937; Second Set, 1902-1912; and Third Set, 1902-1908.
      - First Set, 1890-1937
        Some volumes contain multiple years. Some years overlap across different volumes.
        Volumes covering years prior to 1899 probably document real estate sold in El Paso and Fremont Counties that became part of Teller County.
        Arranged chronologically by sales dates.
        - Tax Sales for 1889-1896, 1890 June 25-1897 December 11 (Box 151, Folder 466)
        - Tax Sales for 1892-1896, 1894 December February 16-1897 December 11 (Box 151, Folder 467)
        - Tax Sales for 1896-1898, 1898 December 5-1899 December 8 (Box 151, Folder 468)
        - Tax Sales for 1893-1899, 1900 December 6-7 (Box 151, Folder 469)
        - Tax Sales for 1896-1900, 1901 November 20 (Box 151, Folder 470)
        - Tax Sales for 1901, 1902 November 17-18 (Box 151, Folder 471)
        - Tax Sales for 1917-1921, 1918 November 22-1922 December 23 (Box 152, Folder 472)
        - Tax Sales for 1922-1925, 1923 December 14-1926 November 20 (Box 152, Folder 473)
        - Tax Sales for 1926-1931, 1927 December 9-1932 December 22 (Box 153, Folder 474)
        - Tax Sales for 1932, 1933 December 4 (Box 153, Folder 475)
        - Tax Sales for 1932-1936, 1934 December 8-1937 December 7 (Box 154, Folder 476)
      - Second Set, 1902-1912
        Manuscript volumes.
        Occasional notes document redemption of tax debts.
        - Book 4 (Cover title 6), 1901, Entries 1-2463, 1902 November 17-18 (Box 155 Oversize)
        - Book 5 (Cover title 7), 1902, Entries 2464-5313, 1903 November 16-17 (Box 156 Oversize)
        - Book 6 (Cover title 8), 1903, Entries 5314-8088, 1904 November 25-26 (Box 157 Oversize)
        - Book 7 (Cover title 9), 1904, Entries 1-2370, 1905 November 25-27 (Box 158 Oversize)
        - Book 8 (Cover title 10), 1905, Entries 2371-5494, 1906 November 28-30 (Box 159 Oversize)
          - Duplicate copy, 1906 November 28-30 (Box 160 Oversize)
        - Book 9 (Cover title 11), 1906, Entries 5495-8596, 1907 November 22-23 (Box 161 Oversize)
        - Book 10, 1907 (Cover title 12), Entries 8597-11737, 1908 November 20-21 (Box 162 Oversize)
        - Book 16, Entries 16053-16830, 1912 November 23-25 (Box 163 Oversize)
      - Third Set, 1902-1908
        - Tax Sale Record, Teller County, Entries 1-2463 and 8597-11737, 1902 November 17-1908 November 21 (Box 164 Oversize)
          First portion documents the sale of property for delinquent taxes November 17-18, 1902, with certificate entries 1-2463.
          Second portion documents the sale of property for delinquent taxes November 20-21, 1908, with certificate entries 8597-9414.
        - Tax Sale Record, Teller County, 1902, Entries 2464-5313, 1903 November 16-17 (Box 165 Oversize)
          Entries kept in a ledger book printed for The Home Insurance Company, New York.
        - Tax Sale Record, Teller County, 1903, Entries 5314-8088, 1904 November 25-26 (Box 166 Oversize)
          Entries kept in a ledger book printed for the Springfield Fire & Marine Insurance Company.
        - Tax Sale Record, Teller County, 1904, Entries 1-2370, 1905 November 25-27 (Box 167 Oversize)
        - Tax Sale Record, Teller County, 1905, Entries 2371-5494, 1906 November 28-30 (Box 168 Oversize)
        - Tax Sale Record, Teller County, 1906, Entries 5495-8596, 1907 November 22-23 (Box 169 (Oversize))
  - Discrete Records from Unidentified Abstract Companies, 1895-1940
    Records created by unidentified abstract companies and other businesses, including the records of a sawmill and hardware store.
    - Expenditures Book and Mine Surveys, 1895 August 1-1953 May 20 (Box 170, Folder 477)
      Pages 2-83 document expenditures in cash and check, August 1, 1895-December 4, 1897.
      Pages 84-132 document surveys of mines, including the Oversight Fraction Lode, April 30-May 1, 1948; the Albertson Lode and Josephine Lode, May 23-June 2, 1948; the Florence Lode, October 20, 1948; and the Fluorspar Lode on May 20, 1953.
    - Location Certificates Book, 1895 December 12-1898 January 29 (Box 171 Oversize)
      Volume of carbon copies of location certificates for lodes in Chaffee County, El Paso County, Fremont County.
      Includes an index to the certificates that includes an alphabetical list of lode names, as well as the claimants and page numbers.
      Several notes are faded and unreadable.
    - Bausman's Quick Index, circa 1895 (Box 172)
      Alphabetical index to the Victor office of an unidentified business.
    - Scrapbook of Legal Notices, 1897 May 15-1901 September 12 (Box 173 Oversize)
      Newspaper clippings of mining and patent applications in the Cripple Creek Mining District published by the United States Land Office, Pueblo, Colorado. The clippings document circa 900 applications.
      Manuscript inscriptions record names of individual lodes and mines.
    - Index to Names, circa 1899 (Box 174)
      Entries grouped alphabetically by the surname or corporate name.
    - Ledger of Customer Accounts and Expenses, 1907-1922 (Box 175 Oversize)
      Possibly a ledger for an abstract company.
    - Ledger, 1915 February 15-1919 May 13 (Box 176)
      Possibly a ledger for an abstract company. It includes an account at the Hamilton National Bank in Denver, Colorado, as well as accounts of expenses, bills payable, cash on hand, rental income, salaries, interest, and profits.
      Many pages are missing from the volume.
    - Ledger, 1936 July-1937 May (Box 177 Oversize)
      Possibly a ledger for an abstract company. It includes an account at the Trust National Bank, cash, ore hauling, drayage, ice, sales, and sales tax, as well as offices in Victor and Cripple Creek.
    - Register of Cash Sales, 1937 June 1-1940 October 30 (Box 178 Oversize)
      Entries include amounts for bran, building material, cash sales, coal, hay, lime, miscellaneous, and sales tax.
      Kept in a ledger for the Security Insurance Company of New Haven, Connecticut, Western Department, Rockford, Illinois.
- Records of Businesses and Organizations, circa 1895-circa1972; Series III; 2.9; (18 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  This series is arranged alphabetically into fifteen subseries for each organization.
  Organizations representated in this series consist of Colorado Trading and Transfer Company; Cripple Creek, City Treasurer; Cripple Creek State Bank; First National Bank of Cripple Creek; Golden Cycle Land Corporation; Gould Consolidated Mining Company; Lind Auto Service; Mary McKinney Mining Company; Mechanics' and Traders' Insurance Company of New Orleans; Mechanics' and Traders' Insurance Company of New Orleans; Pikes Peak Cottage City Corporation; Stratton-Independence Ltd.; United Mine Workers of America; Western Union Telegraph Company; Unidentified Sawmill and Hardware Store, and Unidentified Mines.
  - Colorado Trading and Transfer Company, 1906-1907
    The Colorado Trading and Transfer Company was a drayage company founded by Albert Eugene Carlton that hauled freight from railroad stations into Cripple Creek.
    - Purchase Journal, No. 7, 1906 April 2-1907 December 31 (Box 179 Oversize)
      Includes columns for bran, building material, coal, flour, hay, ice, oats, and miscellaneous.
  - Cripple Creek, City Treasurer, 1897-1899
    The City Treasurer of Cripple Creek had responsibility for managing the funds of the city, as well as issuing and repaying debt.
    - Treasurer Ledger, No. 1, 1897 April 27-1899 April 19 (Box 180 Oversize)
      Documents several municipal accounts including the building fund; contingent fund; dog pound tax fund; election fund; electric light fund; fire department fund; general fund; poll tax fund; printing fund; public library fund; salary fund; sewer tax fund; streets, bridges, and alleys fund; the city clerk, Dallas C. Weyand; the city collectors, C. M. Hoopes and W. L. Smith; the police magistrates, John E. Rinker and H. H. Whiting; and water fund; as well as interest accrued from funds.
  - Cripple Creek State Bank, 1904-1921
    Cripple Creek State Bank was a bank in Cripple Creek, Colorado, November 1904 to January 1921.
    - Cashier's Check Register, 1904 November 9-1921 January 8 (Box 181 Oversize)
      Includes laid-in sheets from a ledger, January 2, 1920, to May 31, 1920.
  - First National Bank of Cripple Creek, circa 1895
    The First National Bank of Cripple Creek was founded by Jim M. Parker in 1893.
    - Index to Ledger, A-L Book, E, circa 1895 (Box 182)
      Includes entries for names, arranged alphabetically.
  - Golden Cycle Land Corporation, circa 1972
    Golden Cycle Land Corporation was a land development company. Between 1970 and 1973, it subdivided an area that became known as Cripple Creek Mountain Estates.
    Arranged sequentially by the numbers applied to subdivisions in the volumes.
    Alphabetical lists of property owners in subdivisions established by the Golden Cycle Land Corporation in Cripple Creek, Colorado.
    - Area 1, circa 1972 (Box 183 Oversize)
    - Areas 4, 5, 6, and 7, circa 1972 (Box 184 Oversize)
  - Gould Consolidated Mining Company, 1901-1925
    Gould Consolidated Mining Company was a mining company in Cripple Creek District, Teller County, Colorado, May 1901-March 1904. It was succeeded by the Gould Mining Company, which operated until April 1912, when it was succeeded by the Kittie Lane Gold Mining Company.
    - Ledger, 1901 May 4-1925 July 22 (Box 185 Oversize)
      Ledger of stock certificates issued and cancelled by the Gould Consolidated Mining Company May 4, 1901, to March 14, 1904, as well as the Gould Mining Company, March 7, 1904, to April 8, 1912, and the Kittie Lane Gold Mining Company, March 8, 1912, to July 22, 1925.
  - Lind Auto Service, 1918-1966
    Lind Auto Service was an automobile repair and welding business in Cañon City, Colorado, circa 1918-1966.
    - Ledger, 1918 May 11-1969 December 10 (Box 186 Oversize)
      Ledger documents ore received and used, May 11, 1918, to May 24, 1919, as well as business income and expenditures January 6, 1944, to December 10, 1969.
    - Ledger, 1929-1966 (Box 187 Oversize)
      Alphabetical ledger of accounts.
      Laid-in receipts document payment for some accounts.
  - Mary McKinney Mining Company, 1906-1907
    The Mary McKinney Mining Company operated in Cripple Creek, Colorado, 1892-1911. It reincorporated in 1912.
    - Voucher Register Book, No. 2, 1906 April 10-1907 December 19 (Box 188 Oversize)
      Documents expenses of the company.
  - Mechanics' and Traders' Insurance Company of New Orleans, 1911
    Mechanics' and Traders' Insurance Company of New Orleans was organized in 1869.
    - Cripple Creek Insurance Policies, 1911 September 2-1918 June 14 (Box 189 Oversize)
      Ledger kept by George T. Wood, an agent in Cripple Creek, Colorado, for the Mechanics' and Traders' Insurance Company of New Orleans. Leaves of the volume include description of insurance policies, as well as affixed copies of the policies.
      Entries and policies arranged chronologically in the volume.
  - Pikes Peak Cottage City Corporation, 1920-1963
    Pikes Peak Cottage City Corporation was a private campground near Colorado Springs, Colorado.
    - Stock Ledger, 1920 June 18-1963 October 23 (Box 190)
  - Stratton-Independence Ltd., 1917-1918
    Winfield Scott Stratton (1848-1902) discovered the Independence Lode near Victor, Colorado on July 4, 1891. In 1900, Stratton sold the Independence Mine to the Venture Corporation of London, incorporated the property as Stratton-Independence Ltd.
    - Mill Dirt Control Book, 1917 May 1-1919 May 12 (Box 191)
      Tally of samples of mill dirt, which represents that ore worked by a mill, probably at the Independence Mill in Victor, Colorado, as well as the quantity of tons of mill dirt processed by the mill, May 1, 1917-May 12, 1919.
  - Teller County Clerk, 1938
    - Direct Primary Election Ballot, Republican Party, Precinct No. 2, Teller County, Colorado, 1938 (Box 192 (Broadside))
      Includes Republican candidates for state and local offices, including Ralph Lawrence Carr (1887-1950) from Cripple Creek, Colorado, for governor. Carr served as the 29th Governor of Colorado, 1939-1943.
  - United Mine Workers of America, 1933
    The United Mine Workers of America is a North American labor union founded in 1890 and known for representing coal miners and coal technicians.
    - Financial Secretary's Cash Book, 1933 December 18 (Box 193 Oversize)
      Blank cash book printed for a local union of the United Mine Workers of America.
      Laid-in sheets, dated December 18, 1933, document local unions in arrears and new transfer books issued to local unions.
  - Western Union Telegraph Company, 1939-1949
    Formed in 1855, Western Union Telegraph Company is a financial services and communications company based in the United States.
    - Ledger of Money Transfers, 1939 September-1949 February (Box 194)
  - Unidentified Sawmill and Hardware Store, 1896-1897
    Journal and ledgers for a saw mill and hardware store, probably in Cripple Creek, Colorado.
    - Journal of Income, 1896 March 2-1897 May 15 (Box 195 Oversize)
      Entries identify the customer account in ledger, as well as merchandise and the dimensions of lumber ordered, the total linear feet of wood, and the cost.
    - Ledger of Customer Accounts, 1896 March 2-1897 May 17 (Box 196 Oversize)
    - Ledger of Customer Accounts, 1897 May 10-1898 July 13 (Box 197 Oversize)
  - Unidentified Mines, circa 1898
    - Ore Book, Lots 1384-1868, circa 1898 April-December (Box 198)
      Assay analyses for ore samples from mines for moisture.
- Records of Individuals, 1901-1926; Series IV; 0.42; (2 boxes)
  This series is arranged alphabetically by the surname of each individual into ? subseries.
  Individuals representated in this series consist of Hildreth Frost and Arthur J. Ventress.
  - Frost, Hildreth, 1901-1926
    Hildreth Frost (1880-1955) was an attorney specializing in mining issues in Teller County, Colorado. Frost was born in Massachusetts, and graduated from Colorado College in 1901 and from Harvard University with a law degree in 1904. Frost also a captain in the National Guard of Colorado and commanded Company A of the Second Infantry, 1911-1916, and served as a Judge Advocate during the southern Colorado Coal Strike, 1913-1914.
    - Opinions on Titles, 1901 May 5-1926 September 1 (Box 199)
      Bound volume with carbon-copies of opinions on titles, which includes opinions written for family members.
  - Ventress, Arthur J., 1903-1904
    This subseries is arranged into a single heading of Account Journals.
    Arthur J. Ventress (1871-1905) was a surveyor and mining engineer. He died in an accident in the Newhouse (Argo) Tunnel in Idaho Springs, Colorado.
    - Account Journals, 1903-1904
      Account journals while working as a surveyor for Clear Creek County, probably based in Georgetown, Colorado. Includes notes on surveys and employees, including James Augustus Ingols (1874-1937), Deems, and Thomas.
      - Journal, 1903 (Box 200, Folder 478)
      - Journal, 1904 (Box 200, Folder 479)
- Maps, 1892-1935; Series V; 0.08; (1 box) + 17 rolls and 4 broadside folders
  Arranged alphabetically by creator.
  Maps that chiefly provide overviews of the Cripple Creek Region, as well as localities and mines.
  Descriptions of scale for individual maps has been applied when readily available.
  - Adams, Jacob R., Map of Goldfield, Colorado, circa 1900; 1 map, 195.5 x 125.5 cm. (Box 201 Roll)
  - Altman Water Company, The Altman Water Works System, Cripple Creek Mining District, Teller County, Colorado, 1900 May; 1 map, 91.1 x 69.8 cm. (Box 202 Roll)
    Map of the pipelines in the water system in the vicinity of West Beaver Creek.
  - Cameron Mines, Land and Tunnel Company, Cameron, Colorado, circa 1898; 1 map, 66.8 x 107.3 cm. (Box 203 Roll)
  - Charles J. Hotchkiss Co., Mining Map of the Cripple Creek District, Colorado. Denver: Chas. J. Hotchkiss, 1933; 2 maps 95 x 91 and 94 x 91 cm. (Box 204 Roll)
    Mining map which documents mines in the Cripple Creek District, Colorado, including the communities of Arequa, Cameron, Cripple Creek, Gillett, and Victor.
    - Duplicate Map, 1933 (Box 205 Roll)
  - Codding, Chas. H., Map of Teller County, 1899; 1 map, 239.5 x 159 cm. (Box 206 Roll)
    Includes county roads, toll roads, railroads, school district boundaries, school lands, and deeded lands.
    Scale: 1 inch to 25000 feet
  - Colwell, Alfred B.
    Alfred Bundy Colwell (1868-1920) was a civil engineer in Cripple Creek, Colorado.
    - Colwell, Alfred B., Map of the Bonanza King Lode: Property of the Gold Hill Bonanza Mining Company, Cripple Creek, Colorado, circa 1900; 1 map, 106 x 257 cm. (Box 207 Roll)
      Scale 1 inch to 40 feet.
    - Colwell, Alfred B., Title Plats of the Midget Gold Mining and Milling Co., Cripple Creek, Colorado, circa 1900; 1 volume. (Box 208, Folder 480-493)
      Disbound volume of plat maps related to the Midget Gold Mining and Milling Co.
      Includes plats for Brayton Lode, Cumberland Lode, Maryland Lode, Midget Lode, Protection Lode, and Sunnyside Lode.
      Scale 1 inch to 200 feet.
  - Colwell, Alfred B., and Edward L. Haff, Map of the Midget Mine, circa 1900; 1 map, 46.6 x 51.3 cm (Box 209 Broadside)
    Scale 1 inch to 100 feet.
  - Davis, Lee W., and Byler, Emmett A.
    Lee W. Davis (born 1866) and Emmett A. Byler (born 1868) operated mine engineering and surveying firms in Colorado and Nevada.
    - Davis and Byler, Approved Mineral Surveys in the Cripple Creek Mining District: Teller County (Formerly Fremont and El Paso Counties), Colorado, Colorado Springs, Colorado: Edward R. March, 1900 January; 1 map, 121 x 91 cm. (Box 210 Broadside)